# **Shailesh Kumar Singh**

Email: shailesh.lucky1987@gmail.com

**Ph:** +91-9718956078

#### PROFESSIONAL SYNOPSIS

A creative & innovative professional with total of 4.5 years + of experience in UI Developer/HTML Developer Experience in front end development technologies and solve cross-browser designing issue.

Ability to quickly grasp any new technologies and concepts.

Coordinating with the other members of both the development team as well as the testing team.

Reliable, motivated, hard working, and attentive to details.

## **KEY SKILLS**

#### **Programming Languages:**

- HTML / XHTML, HTML 5
- CSS ,CSS3
- Div / table less website/ table
- Media Query
- Bootstrap3, Bootstrap4
- Jquery , Javascript, Angular
- Wordpress
- Custom Responsive
- Website Designing according to W3c
- Expert Cross Browser Website Issue
- Agile and Devops process understanding

#### **Software Packages**

- Microsoft Office
- Photoshop
- Dreamweaver
- Notepad++
- Basic Knowledge of github

## **EDUCATION**

- Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science in 2010
- 6 months "Web Designing And Multimedia" from Web Colours, New Delhi

## **EMPLOYMENT**

### **UI and HTML Developer**

Goyal Brothers Publication House | Noida | http: www.goyalsonline.com

## **UI and HTML Developer**

Varbsinfotech pvt Ltd | Noida | http://www.varbsinfotech.com

Nov 2017 to March 2019

## **UI and HTML Developer**

Eazysoftech | Noida | http://www.eazysoftech.com

Oct 2015 to Nov 2017

#### **UI and HTML Developer**

Opusing Ilc | Noida | http://www.opusing.com

June 2014 to Oct 2015

## **PORTFOLIO**

https://www.brighttutee.com

http://www.insurancesrk.com

http://opusing.com

http://www.hartronmotors.com http://www.avntikaconsultancy.in

http://www.100m2.in

http://www.100m2events.com http://www.balajitrips.com http://www.cellark.in http://www.cyberrut.com http://ecotravels.co.nz

http://www.demandlytix.com

**More Website** 

# **PERSONAL DETAILS**

Date of Birth : 01-jan-1987

Father's name : Late. Hridaya Narain Singh

Sex:MaleMarital Status:Single

Languages Known : English & Hindi

Nationality : Indian

### **DECLARATION:**

I hence declare the onus of the credibility of my above mentioned particulars.

Date:

Place: New Delhi (SHAILESH SINGH)